Brianna Goodrich

ISTQB-certified test automation engineer familiar with many software automation and testing tools and programming languages. Former laboratory technician with translatable skills and experiences, ready to build a new career in software QA. Meticulous worker with an eye for detail without losing sight of the big picture.

Lehi, UT 84043 (801) 971-8153 bdlgoodrich@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/brianna-go odrich-377591254

www.github.com/Bdlgoodrich

https://resume-website-briannagoodrichs-projects.vercel.app

EDUCATION

Harvey Mudd College, Claremont, CA — Bachelor of Science, Chemistry

Graduated with distinction

EXPERIENCE

Momentum Gymnastics, American Fork, UT — *Director of Ninja Force*

JAN 2023 - PRESENT

Develop, adapt, and implement flexible lesson plans for Ninja classes with multiple age and skill ranges. Assist coaching SPED gymnastics class, adapting skills and coaching techniques to support students with varying abilities.

Enviropro Laboratories, West Valley City, UT — *Laboratory Technician*

MAY 2011 - JAN 2012

Executed various analytical chemistry methods according to strict regulatory standards. Coordinated with coworkers to ensure accurate results were obtained and reported in a timely manner, in accordance with specified priorities.

University of Utah Dept of Nephrology — Laboratory Technician

SEPT 2008 - FEB 2011

Developed, troubleshot, and performed multiple experiments under limited supervision using a variety of microbiology techniques.

${\bf University\ of\ Utah\ Dept\ of\ Surgery}-{\it Laboratory\ Technician}$

JUNE 2006 - JUNE 2008

Autonomously designed, troubleshot, and performed experimental procedures. Managed product ordering and general laboratory maintenance. Supervised temporary laboratory aides.

SKILLS

Intermediate Java

Intermediate JavaScript

Intermediate C#

Selenium WebDriver

REST Assured API testing

TestNG

Cucumber

Jenkins

Postman

Git source control

Agile/SCRUM

Critical thinking and creative problem solving

Good time management and adaptive prioritization

Highly organized

Detail-oriented

Effective multitasking

ACHIEVEMENTS

ISTQB Certified Test Automation Engineer

Foundational C# with Microsoft Certification